/* Creating an Array containing all the questions and answers in the boolean format */
const questions = [{
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which player has scored the most goals in Champions League history?",
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    options: [
      "Leo Messi",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Robert Lewandowski",
      "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"

    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which player has the most appearances in Champions League history?",
    answer: "Iker Casillas",
    options: [
      "Xavi",
      "Iker Casillas",
      "Raúl",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following players has scored the most goals in the Champions League?",
    answer: "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
    options: [
      "Didier Drogba",
      "Robert Lewandowski",
      "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
      "Filippo Inzaghi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who has won the Champions League with the most different clubs (three)?",
    answer: "Clarence Seedorf",
    options: [
      "Samuel Eto'o",
      "Clarence Seedorf",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Toni Kroos"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which team has scored the most goals (25, season 2017/2018) in a Champions League group stage?",
    answer: "PSG",
    options: [
      "PSG",
      "Real Madrid",
      "Manchester City",
      "Monaco"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many goals did Cristiano Ronaldo score in the 2013/2014 season when he broke a new record for goals in one season in the Champions League?",
    answer: "17",
    options: [
      "15",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who has the most assists in Champions League history?",
    answer: "Ryan Giggs",
    options: [
      "Leo Messi",
      "Ryan Giggs",
      "Xavi",
      "Mesut Özil"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many hattricks have Cristiano Ronaldo and Leo Messi scored in the Champions Leauge?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "4",
      "6",
      "8",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which player has represented the most clubs in the Champions League group stage?",
    answer: "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
    options: [
      "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
      "Javier Saviola",
      "Samuel Eto'o",
      "Hernán Crespo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who has scored the fastest goal in Champions League history?",
    answer: "Roy Makaay",
    options: [
      "Raúl",
      "Fernando Torres",
      "Hernán Crespo",
      "Roy Makaay"
    ]
  }
];